Guide to the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) Records, 1985-2001
Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) Records, 1985-2001
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) records, 1985-2001
7669
Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation.
67 cubic feet
Administrative files, correspondence, newspaper clippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Administrative and subject files, correspondence, media kits, press releases, clippings, and files on the GLAAD Media Award events from the New York City, Atlanta, and Los Angeles offices.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
GLAAD works to ensure fair portrayal of lesbians and gays in all forms of media, from newspapers to major motion pictures.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation.
Subjects:
Gay rights--United States.; Homosexuality on television--United States.; Homosexuality in motion pictures--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. New York Office Administrative Files
Boxes 1-7
Series II. New York Office Media Alerts, Press Releases, and Clippings
Boxes 8-11,20-22, 23-67
Series III. Atlanta Office Administrative Files
Boxes 12-14
Series IV. Atlanta Office Subject and Media Files
Boxes 15-19
Series V. Los Angeles Office Subject and Media Files
Box 22
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. New York Office Administrative Files
  - Administrative files and correspondence, 1985-1999
    - Positive Image Project memo, 1985 (Box 1)
    - History of GLAAD, 1990 (Box 1)
    - History of GLAAD, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Planning documents, 1991-93 (Box 1)
    - Restructuring and Merger (2 folders), 1994 (Box 1)
    - Management Team, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Staff retreat (2 folders), 1999 (Box 1)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence and Media Awards material (10 folders), 1993-98 (Box 1)
    - GLAAD/USA unidentified script (2 folders), 1991 (Box 1)
  - Administrative files, 1991-1994
    - Program reports, by-laws, correspondence, meeting minutes (Box 2)
  - Administrative files, 1993-1996
    - Board of Directors materials, Board Committees, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Development (Box 3)
    - Growth Plan, 1996 (Box 3)
    - Administrative files, Growth Plan, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Administrative files, 1996-1998
    - Board of Directors meeting minutes (Box 5)
    - Finance (Box 5)
  - Administrative files, Subject files, 1996-2000
    - Intranet and Internet: files re: establishing email and a web page and connecting GLAAD offices electronically, 1996-98 (Box 6)
    - October Lesbian and Gay History Month packet, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Project 21, 1996-97 (Box 6)
    - Media Monitor and Response Revitalization Project, 1996-97 (Box 6)
    - "Seen Anything Good Lately" study guide, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Observatory Public Service Announcement, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Media Awards, 1997-2000 (Box 6)
  - Videos
    - "Seen Anything Good Lately?"
      - USE COPY, 1997; VHS; 505 (V-)
      - ARCHIVAL COPY, 1997; VHS (V-)
  - Administrative files, 1997-2000
    - Board of Directors' meeting information and logistics (Box 7)
    - Hate Radio Monitoring Kit (Box 7)
- Series II. New York Office Media Alerts, Press Releases, and Clippings
  - GLAAD Alert, GLAADlines, Press Hits, 1994-1999 (Box 8)
  - GLAAD Alert, GLAADlines, Press Hits, 1996-1999 (Box 9)
  - Clippings, media releases, GLAAD Alert, and "Video Activism," by Gay and Lesbian Mountaineers, distributed by GLAAD, 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Media packets on various topics including Dr. Laura Schlessinger, anti-gay radio personality, and Ellen Degeneres coming out on her TV show on April 30, 1997, 1996-2000 (Box 11)
  - Press kits and programs for GLAAD Media Award shows (Box 11)
  - Cassette tape: "Dr. Laura on... " compiled by GLAAD
    - USE COPY, June-July 1999 (TR-)
    - ARCHIVAL COPY, June-July 1999 (TR-)
  - 20/20, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 21st Century FAX, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - A. Magazine, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Aaron, Hank, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - AB101, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - AB222, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - abcnews.com, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Abortion, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Acadamy of American Poets, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - ACT-UP Protests, 1989-1993, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - ACT-UP Internal Files, 1992, 1996, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - ACT-UP general, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Advertising council, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - A & E, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Africa, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - AIDS, 1986, 1991-1999 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - AIDS related defamation, 1990-1996 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - AIDS, 1996-2000 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - AIDS Conference '92, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - AIDS/HIV, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - AIDS in film/music/video, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - AIDS and lesbians, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - AIDS Memorial Grove, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - AIDS partnerships, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Alliance for Gay and Lesbian Artists, 1985-1986? (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Amedure, Scott, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Amendment 2: Colorado, 19961 (Box 20, Folder 27-28)
  - American Airlines, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - America Family Association (Box 20, Folder 30-32)
  - American Scholar, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Amnesty International, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Anti Defamation League, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Anti Defamation League, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Anti gay material, 1987-1991? (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Anti gay initiatives, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - AOL- Tim McVeigh, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Arkansas Democrat-Gazette, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - As The World Turns TV show, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Athletes, 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - AT & T, 1986,1991,1996,1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - AT & T/Rovira, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Ballot Measure 9, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Bangor Daily News, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Baptist Boycott (Disney), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Basic Instinct movie, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Basic Instinct movie, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Baver, Gary, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mr. Belevedere TV show, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Big Brother (anonymous person sending letters in the name of GLAAD), 1991 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The Birdcage movie, 19968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Bird on a Wire movie, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Bono, Chastity, 1997-1999 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Books, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Bowers, Hardwick: Argument brief, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Bowers, Hardwick: Project signatories, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 22-23)
  - Braveheart movie, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Brothers, Dr. Joyce, 1991,1998 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Bufalino, Jamie, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Burger King, 19908 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Burnstein, Karen, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Bush, George, 1992, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Bush, Barbara, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Business Week, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Cammermeyer, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Campaign '96, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Carlin, George, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Cartoons, 1991-1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Church, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Catholic League, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - CBS TV News (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - CBS TV Records, 1990, 1997, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - CBS Eye On People, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The Celluloid Closet (book, movie), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Censorship, 1988-1990, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Challenge Bigotry/Positive Image, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Charer, Mona, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Charlie Daniels Band, 19898 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Chas/Ellen Hot File, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Cheers TV show, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - The Chief, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Child magazine, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Chrysler, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Clancy, Tom (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Clause 28, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Clause 28: Demonstration, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Clause 28: Press Coverage, 198-7-19888 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Clay, Andrew Dice, 1990-1991, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - CNN, 1991-1992, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Cobb County Olympics, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Colorado Boycott, 1992,1998 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Colorado Ref. '92, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Columbine, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 28-29)
  - Comics, Cartoons: comic strips, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Comics, Cartoons: Leonardo DaVinci, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Comics, Cartoons: Maggie Sawyer, 1995, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Comics, Cartoons: Marvel Comics, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Comics, Cartoons: Media Awards Nominees, 1996? (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Comics, Cartoons: Comedy, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Comics, Cartoons: Comedy Central, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Comics, Cartoons: Comedy Central ( Partners), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Communications Decency Act (CDA), 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Compuserve, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Con Air movie, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Continental Airlines, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Media Clippings Organized Alphabetically by Publication
    - A - Da, 1986-2000 (Box 23)
    - Da - G, 1988-1999 (Box 24)
    - J - N (Box 25)
    - New York B - New York P, 1986-2000 (Box 26)
    - New York P - New York T, 1994-1996 (Box 27)
    - New York T - Newsd, 1986-2000 (Box 28)
    - Newsd - S, 1995-2000 (Box 29)
    - S - U, 1986-2000 (Box 30)
    - W - X and Bound Media Clippings, 1989-1999 (Box 31)
  - Media Clippings Organized Alphabetically By Subject
    - A - C, 1986-2000 (Box 32)
    - C - Di, 1986-2000 (Box 33)
    - Di - Ed, 1990-2000 (Box 34)
    - Ed - Ex, 1990-2000 (Box 35)
    - Ex - Fi, 1990-2000 (Box 36)
    - Fi - Ga, 1986-2000 (Box 37)
    - Ga - Ge, 1989-1999 (Box 38)
    - Ge - Ha, 1988-2000 (Box 39)
    - He - Hu, 1988-2000 (Box 40)
    - I - Jo, 1985-2000 (Box 41)
    - Ju - La, 1986-2000 (Box 42)
    - La - Lo, 1986-2001 (Box 43)
    - Lo - Mc, 1986-2000 (Box 44)
    - Mc - Mi (Box 45)
    - Mi - Na (Box 46)
    - Na - Ni (Box 47)
    - N - Ov, 1986-2000 (Box 48)
    - Ov - Ph, 1986-2000 (Box 49)
    - Po - Ra, 1986-2000 (Box 50)
    - Ra - Ri, 1992-2000 (Box 51)
    - Ri - Sa, 1986-2000 (Box 52)
    - Sa - Sh, 1986-2000 (Box 53)
    - Sh - St, 1990-2000 (Box 54)
    - St - Ti, 1985-2000 (Box 55)
    - Ti - Up, 1986-2000 (Box 56)
    - Up - V, 1990-2000 (Box 57)
    - Vi - Wh, 1986-2000 (Box 58)
    - Wh - Yo, 1989-2000 (Box 59)
    - Yo - Z and Bound Media Clippings, 1987-2001 (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous Press Materials, Correspondence, etc.
    - Media Clippings by Month/Year, 1990-1991 (Box 61)
    - Correspondence, Press Materials, Publications, 1990-1995 (Box 62)
    - Correspondence, Press Releases, Publications, 1990-1995 (Box 63)
    - Correspondence, Press Materials, Publications (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, Press Materials, Publications, 1989-1994 (Box 65)
    - Unsorted Media Clippings And Press Materials (Box 66-67)
- Series III. Atlanta Office Administrative Files
  - Atlanta office administrative files and miscellany ca. 1993-1994
    - Horizon Community Services (Box 12)
    - Press releases, other chapters (Box 12)
    - Clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
    - GLAAD Atlanta phone list (Box 12)
    - Meeting minutes; by-laws; memoranda; media guide; meeting agendas; contact sheet; clippings (Box 12)
  - Administrative files and correspondence (unorganized), Pre-1997 (Box 13)
  - Minutes, by-laws, other administrative files, 1992-1996 (Box 14)
- Series IV. Atlanta Office Subject and Media Files
  - GLAAD ATL 1994 Letters/Memos GLAADLines (Box 15)
  - MONTH (Box 15)
  - ACT-UP (Box 15)
  - Actor's Express (Box 15)
  - AID Atlanta (Box 15)
  - AIDS Survival Project (Box 15)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 15)
  - American Family Association (Box 15)
  - Amnesty International (Box 15)
  - Annual Membership Conference – Fund for Southern Communities. (Box 15)
  - Anti-Defamation League (Box 15)
  - Arrington (Box 15)
  - Arts (Box 15)
  - Asheville Citizens Times (Box 15)
  - Association Executives Human Rights Caucus (Box 15)
  - Atlanta, City Of (Box 15)
  - Atlanta Gay and Lesbian Arts Festival (Box 15)
  - Atlanta Executive Network (Box 15)
  - Atlanta Rainbow Network (Box 15)
  - AJC (Box 15)
  - Augusta Chronicle (Box 15)
  - Banton, Buju (Box 15)
  - Billboard (Box 15)
  - Bisexual (Box 15)
  - Board (Box 15)
  - Books, New (Box 15)
  - Boycott Quarterly (Box 15)
  - Braveheart (Box 15)
  - Buchanan (Box 15)
  - Business (Box 15)
  - Campbell (Box 15)
  - Celluloid Closet (Box 15)
  - Carrollton GA (Box 15)
  - Center For Democratic Renewal (Box 15)
  - Christian Action Network (Box 15)
  - Christian American (Box 15)
  - Christian Film and Television Commission (Box 15)
  - CNN (Box 15)
  - COBB Citizens Coalition (Box 15)
  - Coca-Cola (Box 15)
  - Comedy Central (Box 15)
  - Comics (Box 15)
  - Committment Ceremony Announcements (Box 15)
  - Common Ground (Box 15)
  - Community (Box 15)
  - Computer-Net (Box 15)
  - Consortium on Peace Research, Education and Development (Box 15)
  - Correspondence In (Box 15)
  - Culture Watch (Box 15)
  - Custody (Box 15)
  - Denver (Box 15)
  - Domestic Partnership (Box 15)
  - Dykes and Faggots Bash Back (Box 15)
  - Emory (Box 15)
  - Entertainment (Box 15)
  - Etc. Magazine Contact Us/GLAAD/Atl. (Box 15)
  - Executive Director (Box 15)
  - Facilities (Box 15)
  - F.C.C. (Box 15)
  - Film (Box 15)
  - Finances (Box 15)
  - Florida (Box 15)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 15)
  - Fundraising (Box 15)
  - Fund For Southern Communities (Box 15)
  - Fundraising 2 (Box 15)
  - Gay and Lesbian Americans (Box 15)
  - Gay Entertainment Television (Box 15)
  - Gay and Lesbian, Parents Coalition International (Box 15)
  - Gay Officer’s Action League (Box 15)
  - Gay Games (Box 15)
  - Genetic Gay Genes (Box 15)
  - GAPAC (Box 15)
  - Gay Agenda, The (Box 15)
  - Georgia Advocates for Battered Woman and Children (Box 15)
  - Georgia Psychological Association (Box 15)
  - Georgia Trend (Box 15)
  - GLAAD/NET (Box 15)
  - Government, US (Box 15)
  - GPTV (Box 15)
  - History Thing (Box 15)
  - HIV/AIDS (Box 15)
  - Hollywood Supports (Box 15)
  - Holocaust (Box 15)
  - Homophobia (Box 15)
  - Howell Park (Box 15)
  - Human Rights Action for Health Care (Box 15)
  - Hussain (Box 15)
  - Identity RFD (Box 16)
  - IRS (Proof of nonprofit 501 [c][3] States) (Box 16)
  - Image (Box 16)
  - Incorporation, Certificate Of (Box 16)
  - International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission (Box 16)
  - In the Life (Box 16)
  - Job Discrimination (Box 16)
  - Kansas City (Box 16)
  - KKK (Box 16)
  - LA (Box 16)
  - LA/Newsletter (Box 16)
  - Lambda Center (Box 16)
  - Lambda Legal (Box 16)
  - Landers (Box 16)
  - League (Box 16)
  - League of Gay and Lesbian (Box 16)
  - Lesbian Gay Bisexual Workplace Issues Conference (Box 16)
  - Lesbians (Box 16)
  - Letterhead (Box 16)
  - Lee, Rev. Richard. (Box 16)
  - Limbaugh (Box 16)
  - Lexicon (Box 16)
  - Loftis (Box 16)
  - Log Cabin Republicans (Box 16)
  - March on Washington (Box 16)
  - Moorehouse (Box 16)
  - Mow (Box 16)
  - Materials (Box 16)
  - Market Mark (Box 16)
  - McKinney (Box 16)
  - Men of Little 5 Points (Box 16)
  - Metropolitan Atlanta Community Foundation (Box 16)
  - Metropolitan Community Church (Box 16)
  - Metropolitan Film Society (Box 16)
  - Military (Box 16)
  - Mills, James (Box 16)
  - Minnesota (Box 16)
  - Monitoring and Response (Box 16)
  - National Black Women’s Health Project (Box 16)
  - NGLTF (Box 16)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Journalist Association (Box 16)
  - Navratilova (Box 16)
  - NCA (Box 16)
  - Neighbors Network (Box 16)
  - Nigro (Box 16)
  - Newt (Box 16)
  - GLAAD ATL Newsletter (Box 16)
  - NY (Box 16)
  - GLAAD NY (Box 16)
  - NY City Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project (Box 16)
  - NOW (Box 16)
  - Olympics out of Cobb County 2 (Box 16)
  - Olympics out of Cobb Press Pack (Box 16)
  - NY Reports/Newsletters (Box 16)
  - NY Press Releases (Box 16)
  - Our World Television (Box 16)
  - Out (Box 16)
  - Overlooked Opinions (Box 16)
  - Parents, Friends, Family of Lesbians and Gays (Box 16)
  - People for the American Way (Box 16)
  - Percentage (Box 16)
  - Photos (Box 16)
  - POMO Afro Homos (Box 16)
  - Press Release (Box 16)
  - Price, Deb (Box 16)
  - Pride (Box 16)
  - Pro-Choice (Box 16)
  - Profile (Box 16)
  - Project Open Mind (Box 16)
  - PSA (Box 16)
  - Publications (Box 16)
  - Publications, Georgia (Box 16)
  - Radio and TV News Directors Association (Box 16)
  - Ranks, Shabba (Box 16)
  - Religion (Box 16)
  - Religious Right (Box 16)
  - RIF (Box 16)
  - Same (Box 16)
  - San Diego (Box 16)
  - Science (Box 16)
  - SFBA, GLAAD (Box 16)
  - SFBA, Releases (Box 17)
  - SFBA Project 21 (Box 17)
  - Sebesta (Box 17)
  - Seminar (Box 17)
  - Sex Education (Box 17)
  - Media Conference, FSC (Box 17)
  - South Carolina (Box 17)
  - Speaker's Bureau (Box 17)
  - Straight But Not Narrow (Box 17)
  - Stonewall (Box 17)
  - Straight From the Heart (Box 17)
  - Testing The Limits (Box 17)
  - Theatre (Box 17)
  - Tidings Printed Copies (Box 17)
  - Transgender (Box 17)
  - Tree Atlanta (Box 17)
  - University Georgia (Box 17)
  - USA Activation (Box 17)
  - GLAAD USA (Box 17)
  - USA/By-Laws (Box 17)
  - Transition Committee (Box 17)
  - GLAAD/USA SFBA Conference May 19 (Box 17)
  - Tax Exemptions (Box 17)
  - USA Correspondence (Box 17)
  - USA Conference (Box 17)
  - USA Conference Out (Box 17)
  - USA Conference January 1994 (Box 17)
  - USA Press Release (Box 17)
  - UCLA (Box 17)
  - Venus (Box 17)
  - VIBE (Box 17)
  - USA Personnel (Box 17)
  - Visibility (Box 17)
  - Voices Out Front (Box 17)
  - GLAAD/Vision (Box 17)
  - Workplace (Box 17)
  - WRFG (Box 17)
  - WSB (Box 17)
  - WSB - TV (Box 17)
  - WXIA - TV (Box 17)
  - Wysong (Box 17)
  - Youth (Box 17)
  - Mademoiselle (Box 17)
  - Letters Sent (Box 17)
  - Long Road To Freedom (Box 17)
  - GLAAD New York Newsletter (Box 17)
  - Monitoring and Response Committee (Box 17)
  - Merge (Box 17)
  - GLAAD Alerts (Box 17)
  - GLAAD/National Directory (Box 17)
  - Religious Right (Box 17)
  - GLAAD Members (Box 17)
  - Gay and Lesbian Students and Education (Box 17)
  - Domestic Partners (Box 17)
  - Anti-Gay Initiatives in States History (Box 17)
  - Fight the Right Conference (Box 17)
  - GLAAD Memorandums (Box 17)
  - Fight the Right Stuff to Mail (Box 17)
  - Phone Tree - GLAAD (Box 17)
  - Hotline (Box 17)
  - GLAAD Education Script for Media Workshop (Box 17)
  - The Parents Television Council Advisory Board (Box 17)
  - Drive Time Radio Project (Box 17)
  - Quotes: Religious Right! (Box 17)
  - Religion; ADL, CC, Mel White (Box 17)
  - Fish: Stuff We Have Worked On (Box 17)
  - Civil Rights Organizations (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - GLAAD USA (Box 17)
  - GLAAD USA Memos (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Papers (Box 17)
  - Board Business (Box 17)
  - Clippings (Box 17)
  - Monitoring and Response (Box 17)
  - Members List (Box 17)
  - Letters (Box 17)
  - Newspapers (Box 18)
  - Articles - Padraig McManus McLoughlin, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous Print Articles (Box 18)
  - ABC News (Box 18)
  - Atlanta Journal/Constitution (Box 18)
  - Atlanta Journal - Constitution - Pride (Box 18)
  - Augusta Chronicle (Box 18)
  - GLAAD Media Monitor (Box 18)
  - Clippings September, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Clippings October, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Cobb Campaign (Box 18)
  - Cobb Articles (Box 18)
  - Cobb Articles 2 (Box 18)
  - Copies (Box 18)
  - Creative Loafing (Box 18)
  - Defamation Examples (Box 18)
  - Essence Magazine (Box 18)
  - Fagwatch Letters (Box 18)
  - Fulton County Board of Education (Box 18)
  - Georgia Radio Reading Service (Box 18)
  - Greaseman (Box 18)
  - Grizzard (Box 18)
  - Gwinnett Daily News (Box 18)
  - Hate Laws/Crimes (Box 18)
  - Cobb Articles (Box 18)
  - Memphis Commercial Appeal (Box 18)
  - Articles/GLAAD (Box 18)
  - Nancy Schaefer (Box 18)
  - National Lesbian Caucus Position Papers (Box 18)
  - New York Times (Box 18)
  - Hatred in Georgia 1989 Report (Box 18)
  - New York City Mayor's Gay and Lesbian Report (Box 18)
  - Queer Action Caucus (Box 18)
  - Queer Action Caucus/ON Letter to Lynn Articles (Box 18)
  - Pride Speeches Articles Reactions (Box 18)
  - PBS (Box 18)
  - People TV Cable 12 (Box 18)
  - Panther Patrols (Box 18)
  - Tifton Gazette (Box 18)
  - Southern Voice Contract with Glaad New York (Box 18)
  - Rockdale Citizen (Box 18)
  - Queer Nation Utah (Box 18)
  - Queer Nation San Francisco (Box 18)
  - Queer Nation/Atlanta Newsletter (Box 18)
  - Time Magazine Clippings (Box 18)
  - Queer Nation Atlanta Stationary (Box 18)
  - US News and World Report (Box 18)
  - USA Today (Box 18)
  - Vitae (Box 18)
  - Vanity Fair (Box 18)
  - WAGA TV 5 (Box 18)
  - WKHX (Box 18)
  - WGNX - TV 46 (Box 18)
  - WGST Radio 640 (Box 18)
  - WSB Radio 750 AM (Box 18)
  - WTLK - TV (Box 18)
  - WSB - TV (Box 18)
  - WXIA - TV 11 (Box 18)
  - CALL/WRITE/VOTE, T-Shirt (Box 18)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation, Banner (Box 18)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 19)
- Series V. Los Angeles Office Subject and Media Files
  - Clippings from Outweek magazine (Box 22, Folder 42)
SEPARATED MATERIAL: Includes comic books from the "Comics, Cartoons" files in Series II. New York Office Media Alerts, Press Releases, and Clippings.
Tales of the Closet, published by the Hetrick-Martin Institute, v.1 nos.1-5, 1987-1990
Seven Miles A Second by David Wojnarowicz and James Romberger, 1996
Love and Rockets #50, Fantagraphics Books, 1996
Death. Gaiman, Neil, et. al. DC Comics: 1994
Real War Stories: Citizen Soldier, Eclipse Books, 1991
Metropolis S.C.U.: Special Crimes Unit, DC Comics, 4 issue mini-series, nos. 1-4, Nov.1994-Feb.1995
Northstar, Marvel Comics, v.1, nos.3-4 of 4, June-July 1994
Chiaroscuro: The Private Lives of Leonardo Da Vinci, DC Comics, Nos. 1-9, July 1995-Mar.1996
Quarantines and Death: The Far Right's Homophobic Agenda, by Mab Segrest and Leonard Zeskind, published by Center for Democratic Renewal and Education, 1991
This Week in Texas, Volume 20, Number 29, September 23-29, 1994, published by Texas Weekly Times Newspaper Company
World: The Journal of the Unitarian Universalist Association, Volume 8, Number 4, July/August 1994
World: The Journal of the Unitarian Universalist Association, Volume 8, Number 5, September/October 1994
A Magazine: The Asian American Quarterly, Volume 2, Number 3, Fall 1993
The Advocate, Issue 711, July 9, 1996
Out, Number 15, September 1994
Southern Forum, Volume 2, Number 13, July 1, 1994
Alternatives: National Lesbian and Gay Journalists Association, Volume 4, Number 3, Summer 1994
1994 Atlanta Lesbian and Gay Pride Official Commemorative Program, June 1994, Official Commemorative Program for the 1994 Atlanta Pride Celebration, published by Southern Voice and The Atlanta Lesbian and Gay Pride Committee